# **Bodin Punyaprateep**

bodin.punyaprateep@gmail.com ◆ linkedin.com/in/bpunyaprateep 26 Sawdon Drive, Whitby, ON ♦ Cell (905) 442-4821 ♦ Home (905) 576-1614

### CUSTOMER SERVICE PROFESSIONAL

~ Background in Business management and Customer Relations ~

Dedicated professional with two years of customer service experience in a variety of settings. Effective communication skills aimed at understanding the needs of clients and directing them to the appropriate services. Strong problem solving and organizational skills developed from participation with not-for-profit business organizations like DECA. Skilled in developing rapport with clients and maintaining engagement. Technically savvy in the following applications: Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, and Programming Languages: HTML, CSS/SASS, JS, Python, R. Additional areas of strengths include:

- Able to type at 90 wpm with high accuracy
- Highly motivated and results driven
- Proficient in MS Office applications
- Effective listener and communicator
- Professional, friendly demeanour
- Strong problem solving skills

#### PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

# Website Admin/Manuscript Editor | Freelance Work

2016 – Current

- Managed client websites by ensuring up-time and other systems administrator duties.
- Managed client's email and social media, maintaining a professional appearance.
- Provided consultation on the copy editing and design of client websites and books.
- Prepared manuscript and novel materials for publishing on behalf of the client.

## **Business Analyst** | Brooklin Bulletin Signs and Custom Printing

2015

- Researched and implemented a Management Information System to maximize efficiency for the company.
- Conferred with clients and management to identify and document requirements to provide business solutions.
- Dictated training manuals for the Management Information System and trained production and administrative staff on its proper use.
- Responsible for auditing professional e-mails to ensure accurate invoice procedures.

# **Kitchen Assistant** | DeSiam Thai Restaurant

2008 - 2012

- Maintained the cleanliness and overall appearance of the restaurant on a daily basis.
- Maintained effective communication with coworkers and staff to ensure customer's orders were accurate and delivered in a timely fashion.
- Responsible for following food safety practices to ensure a hygienic work place.
- Plated and packaged all food orders outgoing from the kitchen and for various take-out orders.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Technology** | Ryerson University

2012 - 2016

Graphic Communications Management with a focus on management for the printing industry